&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我总结一下double equals是如何工作的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let me summarize how double equals works.
这是算法的摘要，您可以阅读算法，但它是摘要。
This is summary of the algorithm, you can read the algorithm but it's summary.
如果相同的类型，它将只使用三重等于。
If the types of the same it's just gonna use triple equals.
如果它们中的任何一个都不是或未定义的，则它们是相等的。
If either of them both of them are no or undefined, they are equal.
如果比较中涉及非原语，
If there are non primitives involved in the comparison,
他们总是首先变得原始。
they are always gonna become primitive first.
一旦你有了基元，你就更喜欢数字了。
And then once you have primitives prefer to number.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我很乐观，相信每个开发人员
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I'm just optimistic enough to believe that every developer
来自具有两周JavaScript经验的初级开发人员，
from the junior developer with two weeks of experience in JavaScript,
拥有20多年经验的开发人员，
up to the experienced developer with 20 plus years,
可以理解这样一个相当简单的系统。
can understand a fairly straightforward system like that.
通过了解它，避免出现问题的地方。
And by understanding it, avoid the places where it can be problematic.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么那些有问题的案例是什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So what are those problematic cases?
其中很多是我们已经看过的，但是让我们来谈谈角落里的案例，
Many of these are ones we've already seen, but let's talk about the corner cases,
我们得谈谈他们这样我们才能避开他们。
we gotta talk about them so that we can avoid them.